And then I decide where to go and take care of the crew.
So I'm the manager of the carriage.
Today we will answer some questions.
And for that we have an iPad to help.
"Is there any trait that many people think you have to have but that is not really that important?"
Here, the cliché will be big, strong, bite.
But you don't have to be so big and strong.
Nah.
For most positions I would say.
Yes, so I still think that some kind of fitness and want you probably need to have the foundation to cope with it.
Because it gets tough.
- Yes, it gets pretty physical.
The worst is probably then when I went to and from the garage, over and over again.
But it is for a longer period.
The best thing was when I was at a shooting exercise in Älvdalen.
Then it was brilliant sunshine, completely crispy outside.
So we went up to a small height with pretty good views, and then we stood and shot there for several hours.
It was nice.
Drinking coffee and had gotten thread.
Luxurious anyway.
Being able to have it as an everyday life sometimes.
-And you?
I've been thinking about that question quite a few times.
The toughest thing is probably still the last exercise "never give up", is it called?
Type a form of basket test?
Or?
- Yes ... but you can say.
Where did you have many of your exercises.
Pure geographically?
Älvdalen, then it was Skåne and Skövde.
Great question.
I'm from the army so I wear green.
It fits great in the forest.
I am blue like the sea, so the Navy I come from.
And that's where I did my military duty too.
Then the Navy is quite scattered.
And the Navy also has green uniform.
Especially in the field.
And I had that during the first few months.
Yes, everyone has, I think.
Now it rang.
"Is there any difference in the requirements or tasks for men and women under the military duty?"
Nah.
I wouldn't say that.
According to the duty and testing authority, this is the same requirement.
It doesn't matter if you are a guy or a girl.
Everyone is the same, it's just that everyone is different individuals.
That's really what you see.
Yes, but really.
One more, really.
"What happens when you have mucked? Am I free then or what do I have obligations afterwards?"
Muck is kind of like a student after high school.